Jingdai Yang

6127 Pershing Ave Apt#2E, St. Louis, MO 63112 (314) 603-3968

jingdaiyangyang@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Motivated, disciplined M.S. in Electrical System Engineering candidate with technical programming experience. Strong desire to contribute in Software Development Area, design or technical support function utilizing my experience and education as a full time employee. Be familiar with SODC, OOD programming, unit testing and mocking frameworks. Willing to travel and relocate. Available May 2014.

IT SKILLS

• Programming Language Java, Objective-C • Web Development HTML, CSS, PHP, JavaScript, Python • Database MySQL, PostgreSQL • Operation Systems Windows 7/8, Mac OS X, Linux

• Software Eclipse, Matlab, Microsoft Office, Adobe Photoshop

EDUCATION

Washington University in St.Louis

Expected Graduation: May 2014 **Electrical Engineering** Master

Core Courses: Algorithms and Data Structures, Operating Systems Organization, Database Management Systems

Southwest Jiaotong University (China) 2008 - 2012

Electrical Engineering Bachelor

Advanced Computer Courses: Advanced Mathematics, Objected-Oriented Programming and Foundations of Computer Application

RESEARCH EXPERIENCE

Bluetape (Samsung) 2013/06 - 2013/09Wash.U

• Lead WebAPI/Framework/SQL Group and Android App Group

- Used MySQL to build the database and use Java for the Android App and the server (both the socket server and the HTTP server)
- Implemented the functions of this project in Java and the web development technologies

A Comparative Study on The Performance of The Parallel Distributing Computing Operation in Java and MatLab

2013/09 - Present Wash.U

Chengdu

- Solved computationally and data-intensive problems in Java thread and Matlab using processors and computer clusters including: High-level constructs—parallel for-loops, special array types, and parallelized numerical algorithms
- Compare the efficiencies and the accuracies of these 2 methods (Java and MatLab)
- Goals: Apply the result of the study to cloud computing for App in smartphones and in the super computer in Wash.U to improve the efficiency for solving complex computations and problems

Myamazon Web Application

2013/11 Wash.U

- Built an E-Commerce website like A mazon with HTML, PHP and some other web technologies
- Used MySQL to build the database to store the data about the item information, the comment, the rate and the advertisements
- Added function so customers could use PayPal for purchases

Bookstore Web Application

Dow Jew InfoTech, LLC

2013/12

• Built servlet and implemented functions and connections to database in Java and JSP

• Built the database for all data including book information, customer information in PostgreSQL

2014/01 Saint Louis

- Built the official webpage for Dow Jew InfoTech, LLC (http://www.sapapotraining.com)
- Built an IOS application to help customers to make an order easily with the instructions and show the company's information

WORK EXPERIENCE

Luoyang Substation and Luoyang Longmen HSR station (Engineer Assistant)

2011/07 Luoyang

- Solved some problems about the insulation-aging rate and the insulation allowance
- Helped the employees to fix the different kinds of transformers, check the process flows of dynamo manufacturing

Wash.U Engineering Information Technology (Consultant)

2013 - Present

Saint Louis

Wash.U

- As a consultant, answer customers' questions and solve problems about the software, the VPN, the computers Security
- Assist employees to check and maintain computers in Engineering Department Labs